Guide to the PricewaterhouseCoopers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Price Waterhouse Series I: Cataloged Documents
  - Subseries I.4: George O. May Files
    - Sub-subseries I.4.1: Arranged Correspondence
      - Murphy, Mary E.; Richardson, A. P.; Dickinson, Sir Arthur Lowes, 1941-1951 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Gay, Edwin F.; Hatfield, Henry R.; Sanders, T. H.; Dickinson Lectures, 1937-1953 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Baker, John C.; Berger, R. O.; Blackie W.; Finley, R. O.; Hatch, Boyd; Dalton, H. G.; Hoxsey, J.M.B.; Sanders, T. H.; Disclosure in Financial Statements, 1926-1956 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Dividends, 1929 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Dividends-Stock, 1936-1944 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Weisenberger, Arthur Dividends-Stock, 1947-1959 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - Sullivan, M.; Walsh, Anne; Dun & Bradstreet, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - Byerly, F.; Epstein, Ralph C.; Earnings, 1927-1960 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Brett, George P. Eastman, George, 1952 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Berle, Adolph A.; Donham, Dean W. B.; Msy, George O.; O'Hara, John F.; Roberts, George; Schneider, T.; Hunt, Bishop C.; Gay, Edwin F.; New York Times. Economic Conditions-United States, 1920-1956 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Barton, Bruce.; Caulcutt, John; Collins, Edward H.; Copland; Hunt, Bishop C.; Knauth, Oswald W.; Kuznets, Simon Economic Policy, 1934-1953 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Knauth, Oswald W.; Economic Theory, 1953 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Baker, G. Derwood.; Leffingwell, R. C.; MacMillan, O. Townsend; Sachs, Alexander.; Wasson, R. G.; New York Evening Post. Economics, 1921-1953 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Hunt, Bishop C.; Crowther, Geoffrey; Merrifield, Cecil; Robertson, Dennis; Economics, 1954-1960 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Benton, William B. Entrepreneurship, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Hunt, Bishop C.; Roberts, George.; Charles Merz. New York Times. Excess Profits Tax, 1940 -1950 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Barber, Sidman I.; Dohr, James L.; Priest, A. J. G.; Sanders, Thomas H.; Tietjen, A. C. Federal Power Commission, 1944-1958 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Brundage, P. F. Federal Reserve System (revision of), 1929 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Groves, Harold M. Finance-Public, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Armory, Robert; Bedford, Norton M.; Cullen, W. G.; Graham, Willard J.; Inglis, John B.; King, Earle C.; Kuhn, Harold A.; Brett, George P.; Seidman, J. S.; Columbia Law Review; Columbia University Financial Accounting, 1943-1961 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Alban, Frederick J.; Blackie, W.; Carey, John L.; Heaton, W. C.; Wyon, Albert; Becker, A G.; Burling, Edward B.; Demarest, Rosemary; Johnston, V. A.; McInnerney, Thomas H.; Prickett, A. L. Goodyear Tire & Rubber Company. Financial Statements, 1928-1961 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Brundage, P. F.; nglis, John B. Financial Statements-Consolidated, 1929-1960 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Fiske, Wyman P. Ford Foundation, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Finley, John L.; Kelley, Nicholas; Roosevelt, Kermit; Swope, Gerard; Foreign Policy, 1925-1948 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Flagg, H. J. Franchise, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Bevis, Herman W.; Cole, Arthur H.; Heaton, Herbert; Cole, Arthur H.; Halsey, Laurence e.; Heaton, Herbert; Morgan, Shepard; Shaw, Arch W.; Gay, Edwin F., 1930-1961 (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - David, Donald K. Goodwill, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Barton, Bruce; Dewhurst, J. Frederic.; Kerrigan, Harry D. Government, 1938-1961 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Haig, Robert M. Government Expenditures, 1933 (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Great Britain-Companies Act, 1933 (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Clay, F. Henry. Great Britain-Taxation, 1953 (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - Amory, Robert.; McKinley, E. B.; Copeland, Melvin; David, Donald K.; Donham W. B.; Hosmer, W. A.; Harvard University-Graduate School of Business Administration, Harvard University, 1923-1949 (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - Claire, Richard S. Illinois Society of CPA's, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - Adams, T. S.; Gilman, Stephen; Hunt, Bishop C.; McLaren, N. Loyall.; Haig, Robert M.; Jaureguy, A.; Magill, Roswell; Mitchell, Wesley C.; Olds, Irving S.; Sanders, T. H.; Income, 1921- 1943 (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - Broad, Samuel J.; Davis, Hiram S.; Greer, Howard C.; Inglis, John B.; Sanders, T. H.; Burgess, Randolph; Williams, R. W.; Income, 1945-1948 (1-5) (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Bailey, George D.; Bloodsworth, A. J.; Bray, F. Sewell; Brundage, Percival F.; Court, Andrew T.; Greer, Howard C.; Palmer, E. B.; Roberts, George B.; Wilcox, Edward B.; Williams, John H.; Woodward, Donald B. the Accountant. Income, 1948 (6-13)-1949 (1-2) (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Brundage, Percival F.; Davis, H. S.; du Pre, Derek.; Jones, Ralph C.; Keeling, Ralph Franklin; Sanders, T. H.; Income, 1949 (3-11) (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Alexander, Sidney; Carey, John L.; Gilman, Stephen; Knauth, Oswald.; Merz, Charles; Nourse, E. W.; Seligman, Eustace; New York Times. Income, 1949 (12-18)-1950 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Brundage, Percival F.; Greer, Howard C.; Howitt, Harold.; Lawson, W. H.; Mills, Leslie; Smith, Frank B.; Spencer, Timothy.; Townsel, Oscar J.; Alexander, Sidney; Armory, Robert; Bonbright, James C.; Fox, Bertrand; Hill, Thomas M.; Income, 1951-1953 (1-4) (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Barrowcliff, C. Percy.; Bray, F. Sewell; Brundage, Percival F.; Demarest, Rosemary.; Gordon, Myron J.; Broad, S. J.; Robson, Thomas; Income, 1953 (5-7)-1956 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Hanson, George O.; Hanson, Kermit O.; Jaszi, George; Loring, Arthur M.; Rappaport, Percy.; Sprouse, Robert T.; Demarest, Rosemary; Jennings, Alvin R.; Knauth, Oswald W.; Paton, William A.; Pelej, Joseph; Tietjen, A. Carl; Income, 1957-1958 (1-5) (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Aoyagi, Bunji; Cannon, Arthur M.; Inglis, John; Jennings, Alvin R.; Seidman, J. S.; Bonbright, James C.; Daly, T. F. Gilroy; Powell, Weldon; Slichter, Sumer H.; Income, 1958 (6-14)-1959 (1-4) (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Brown, Courtney C.; Norman, H. G.; Seidman, J. S.; Barr, Andrew; Powell, Weldon; Income, 1959 (5-6)-1961 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Chamberlain, Henry T.; Leroy, P. E. H.; Sanders, T. H.; Williams, R. W.; Income Statements, 1934-1945 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Andrews, T. Coleman; Rukeyser, Merryle S.; Seligman, Edwin R. A.; Bonbright, James C.; Brundage, Percival F.; Gay, Edwin F.; Hunt, Bishop C.; Knight, Paul K.; Noyes, C. Reinhold; A.I.A. Committee on Accounting Procedure. Income Tax, 1935-1951 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Carey, John L.; Magill, Roswell; Willard, Wallace W.; Woodward, P. D.; Webster, Blanchard & Willard Co.; Journal Of Accountancy; Rocky Mountain Law Review. Income Tax, 1953-1961 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Bailey, George D.; Couchman, Charles B.; Cranstoun, William D.; Dohr, James L.; Farrand, George N.; Herrick, Anson.; Knight, Paul K.; McLaren, N. Loyall.; Paton, W. A.; Peloubet, Maurice E.; Scovill, H. T.; Stans, Maurice H.; Staub, Walter A.; Income Tax-Accounting, 1944-1948 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Income Tax-Capital Gains Tax. (Memorandum by G. O. May), 1935 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Hayers, Henry R.; Reuther, Walter P.; Seatree, W. E.; Brundage, Percival F.; Fertig, Lawrence; Jones, Ralph C.; Kirkbride, Franklin B.; Knight, Paul K.; W. H. S. Stevens; Gow, J. Steele Yale University; Academy of Political Science; Maurice and Laura Falk Foundation. Inflation, 1935-1951 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Bower, Frank.; Cumberland, W. W.; Cummings, A. T.; Howitt, Harold.; Jessiman, J. M. Inflation, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Cannon, Arthur M.; Higgins, Thomas J.; Hood, Alexander.; Brundage, Percival F.; Howitt, Harold; Inglis, John B.; Jennings, Alvin R.; Kerrigan, Harry D.; Stone, J. R. N.; Wise, T. A. Fortune magazine Inflation, 1957-1960 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Broad, Samuel J.; Edis, Denis.; Freeman, E. Stewart.; Heyworth, Geoffrey.; Konkle, Alexander; Mason, Perry Inflation-Accounting, 1947-1953 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Cannon, Arthur M.; Dohr, James L.; Milroy, Roy.; Paternost, Emmerico.; Powell, Weldon; Inglis, John B.; Smith, Frank P.; Inflation-Accounting, 1954-1961 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Lawson, W. H.; MacIver, Alan S.; Paternost, Emmerico.; Robson, Thomas B.; Wilkinson, F. M.; Institute of Chartered Accountants of England and Wales, 1949-1958 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Insurance Companies, 1936 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Carey, John L.; MacIver, Alan S.; Robson, T. B. International Congress of Accountants, 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Sanders, T. H.; Gay, Edwin F.; Stevens, W. H. S.; Interstate Commerce Commission, 1928-1948 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Bailey, George D.; de Paula, F. R. M.; Gilbert, Morton.; Nissley, Warren W.; Noxon, Frank W.; Sanders, T. H.; Walker, Ross G. A.I.A. Committee on Terminology. Inventories, 1936-1947 (1-3) (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Butters, Keith.; Sanders, T. H.; Ballantine, Arthur A.; Cobren, George M.; Jones, Ralph C.; Kuznets, Simon S.; Woodlief, Thomas; Harvard University Inventories, 1947 (4-5)-1949 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Bevis, Herman W.; Demarest, Rosemary; Jennings, Alvin R.; Mason, Perry; Robson, Thomas B.; the Accountant. Inventories, 1953-1961 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Papworth, W. S.; Bird, Roland.; Blackie, W.; Brundage, Percival; Butters, J. Keith; Jaszi, George; Graham, Willard J.; Hills, George S.; Wilcox, Edward B.; Journal of Accountancy; Price Waterhouse & Co., London. Inventories-Last-in First-out Method, 1947-1951 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Bevis, Herman W.; Mills, Leslie; Moonitz, Maurice; Seidman, J. S.; Noyes, Charles E. Journal of Accountancy; Inventories-Last-in First-out Method, 1953-1961 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Brett, George P.; Sterrrett, Walter; Investments and Securities, 1924-1935 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Hanbury-Williams, J. C. Investments and Securities-Foreign in US, 1942 (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - DeMond, Chester. Investment Companies (Proposed restatement of Regulation S-X. Letter to the A.I.A. Committee on Accounting Procedure.), 1944 (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - Ballantine, Arthur A.; Carey, John L.; Carver, Charles; Mears, Robert M. Journal of Accountancy, 1930-1942 (1-4) (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Mears, Robert M.; Smith, Alden C.; Andreas, Roy; Carey, John L.; Foye, Arthur B.; Papworth, W. S.; Journal of Accountancy, 1942 (5-6)-1953 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Aoyagi, Bunji.; Blough, Carman G.; Demarest, Rosemary.; Noyes, Charles E.; O'Rourke, Ann; Carey, John L.; Lucas, Joan C.; McCormack, Patricia; Journal of Accountancy, 1954-1958 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Noyes, Charles E.; Bevis, Herman W.; Herz, T.; Inglis, John B.; Rappaport, Percy; Journal of Accountancy, 1959-1961 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Bancroft, John C.; Berle, Adolph A.; David, Norman H.; Hotchkiss, H. Stuart.; Ljungberg, F.; Carlberg, S; Greenbaum, Edward S.; May, George O.; Murphy, M. P.; Debenture Holders Protection Committee. Kreuger & Toll Case, 1935 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Labor Unions, 1952 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Grady, Paul; Griswold, Erwin N.; Herz, T.; Marshall, L. C.; Seidman, J. S.; Harvard University-Law School; Harvard Law Review Law, 1930-1961 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Law Firms, 1948 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Bernheimer, Charles L. Legal Aid Society of NYC, 1930 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Blough, Carman G. Liabilities-Contingent, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Brett, George. Littleton, A. C., 1952 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Grady, Paul; Inglis, John B. Management Consultants, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Meyer, Jerome S. Mathematics, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Aoyagi, Bunji; deMare, George.; Gardner, Gordon F.; Hart, Alfred C.; Parker, W. E.; Seidman, J. S.; Dean, Arthur; Freeman, Herbert C.; Powell, Weldon; May, George O. (including account of Mr. May's death), 1952-1961 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Money-International Aspects, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Ahlgren, Lloyd C.; Moon, J. N.; National Association of Cost Accountants, 1942-1950 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Bailey, George D.; Burns, Arthur F.; Carson, William J.; Eakin, Franzy.; Epstein, Ralph C.; Gay, Edwin F.; Burns, Arthur F.; Carson, William; Knauth, Oswald.; Kuznets, Simon; Wolman, Leo; National Bureau of Economic Research, 1933-1949 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Carson, William J.; Collins, E. H.; Cooper, Louise; Fabricant, Solomon; Smith, Datus C. National Bureau of Economic Research, 1952-1956 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Aldrich, Winthrop W.; Ritchie, J. A.; Sokolsky, George E.; Lenhart, Robert F.; Cannon, Arthur M.; Lenhart, Robert F.; Cannon, Arthur M.; National Income, 1944-1958 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Clay, Henry.; Haskell, John.; Securities and Exchange Commission; Federal Power Commission New York Stock Exchange, 1943-1954 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Hoxsey, J. M. B. New York Stock Exchange-Committee on Stock List, 1938 (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - Bevis, Herman H. New York Times, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - Dimock, E. J.; Hartwig, Lawrence E.; Rose, Chapman.; Office of Contract Settlement, 1948-1949 (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - Collins, Edward H.; Friedman, Elisha M.; Anderson, George A.; Rudick, Harry J.; New York Times Pensions and Benefit Plans, 1944-1949 (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - Robson, Thomas B.; Spencer, M. C.; Waterhouse, Nicholas; Berger, Robert O.; Brodie, A. B.; Price Waterhouse & Co., 1928-1954 (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - McIngersoll, Ralph; Horn, Florence.; Larsen, Roy E.; Fortune Magazine Price Waterhouse & Co.-Clients ( includes Kreuger & Toll Case), 1933 (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - Gardner, G. F. Price Waterhouse Foundation, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 27)
      - Inglis, John B.; Richards, J. E.; Waterhouse, Nicholas; Webster, Norman E.; Robson, Thomas.; Spencer, M. C.; Sterrett, J. E.; Price Waterhouse & Co.-History, 1929-1958 (Box 67, Folder 28)
      - Inglis, John B.; Bevis, Herman W. Price Waterhouse & Co.-History, 1959-1961 (Box 67, Folder 29)
      - Wilson, Charles E. General Motors Corporation Productivity, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Bray, F. Sewell; Forster, A.; Sanders, T. H.; Dean, Joel; Harris, Seymour E.; Inglis, John B.; Keown, K. C.; Paul, Randolph; Profit, 1948-1957 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Adams, T. S.; Barber, Sidman I.; Bechtel, Edwin DeT.; Carey, John L.; Cropley, C. Elmore; Dohr, James L.; Donovan, William J.; Farrand, George N.; Freeman, Herbert C.; Gordon, Spencer.; Horne, Henry A.; Nelson, L. R.; Priest, A. J. G.; Sanders, T. H.; Potomac Electric Power Compan Public Utilities, 1930-1945 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Barry, David.; Bonbright, James C.; Echols, A. B.; Grady, Paul.; Oates, James F.; Ross, Clarence H.; Roswell, David S.; Stanley, Hubert A.; Young, H. S.; Sanders, T. H.; Demarest, Rosemary Price Waterhouse & Co., St. Louis; Public Utilities, 1947-1955 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Barr, Andrew; Grady, Paul.; Griffiths, R. M.; Humphrey, George; Inglis, John B.; Knauth, Oswald W.; Mills, Leslie; Paton, William A.; Robson, Thomas; Public Utilities, 1956-1960 (1-2) (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Barr, Andrew; Grady, Paul; Mills, Leslie; Griffiths, R. M.; Nye, Paul E.; Biegler, J. C. Public Utilities, 1960 (3-11)-1961 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Burks, Robert; Inglis, John B.; Paton, William A.; Stanley, Hubert. Public Utilities-Accounting, 1952- 1957 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - National Association of Railroad and Utilities Commissioners. Committee on statistics and accounts of public utility companies. Public Utilities-Uniform System of Accounting, 1939 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Bonbright, James; Chamberlin, E. H.; Taussig, F. W.; Quarterly Journal of Economics, 1929-1954 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Bourne, Edward W.; Parmelee, Julius H. Railroads, 1942-1947 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Altschul, Frank; Belser, A. A.; Berger, R. O.; Berle, Adolph A.; Carey, John L.; Gale, Frank A.; Howard, Stanley E.; Railroads-Accounting, 1927-1941 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Carey, John L.; Jacobus, Alma.; Leslie, Eric A.; Mears, Robert M.; Norman, H. G.; Taft, Walter J.; Vaughan, B. M.; Bunnell, Edward H.; Parmelee, J. H.; Stanley, Hubert A.; Stevens, W. H. S.; Stodghill, W. L.; Tobin, T. J.; Wilkinloh, W. E.; Railroads-Accounting, 1942-1948 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Burns, Garrett T.; Friedman, Elisha M.; MacFarlane, Robert S.; Stevens, W. H. S.; Journal of Accountancy; New York Times. Railroads-Accounting, 1949-1957 (1-3) (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Inglis, John B.; Jennings, Alvin R.; Cannon, Arthur M.; Spacek, Leonard; Railroads-Accounting, 1957 (4-7)-1959 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Hunt, Bishop C. Sales, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Hill, Henry P. Sampling (Statistical Methods), 1958 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Altschul, Frank; Clifford-Turner, H. C.; Frankfurter, Felix.; Gay, Edwin F.; Mead, George H.; Weinberg, Sidney J.; Herlands, William B.; Securities Act of 1933, 1933-1950 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Altschul, Frank.; Burns, John J.; Covington, J. Harry.; Douglas, William O.; Fernald, H. B.; Hatfield, Henry Rand.; Healy, Robert E.; Hunt, B. C.; Kennedy, Joseph P.; Renn, Louis H.; Stanley, Harold.; Securities and Exchange Commission SEC, 1934 (1-10) (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Hunt, Richard C.; Landis, James M.; Neff, Harold H.; Starkey, R. F.; Securities and Exchange Commission SEC, 1934 (11-15) (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Brassor, Francis P.; Burns, John J.; Campbell, S. W.; Gifford, Walter S.; Hoxsey, J. M. B.; Kennedy, Joseph P.; Landis, James M.; Rowland, Stanley W.; Sanders, T. H.; Starkey, R. F.; Weinberg, Sidney J.; Werntz, William W.; White, R. D.; Securities and Exchange Commission SEC, 1935-1939 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Brownell, George A.; Carey, John L.; Dohr, James L.; Grady, Paul; Halsey, Lawrence; Hazlitt, Henry; Jaureguy, A; Pohl, Frank; Werntz, William W.; Securities and Exchange Commission; New York Times. SEC, 1941-1947 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Barr, Andrew; Bevis, Herman W.; Biegler, John C.; Brundage, Percival F.; Davis, Chester C.; Haskell, John.; Herz, T; King, Earle C.; Powell, Weldon.; Seidman, J. C.; Securities and Exchange Commission SEC, 1950-1961 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Dulles, Allen W. The Economist Security Exchanges, 1935 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Baldwin, Henry de Forest; Gay, Edwin F. Ships and Shipping, 1922 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Hutton, Edward F. Socialism, 1949 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Inglis, John B. Spacek, Leonard, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Hunt, Bishop C. Statistics, 1941-1960 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Dalton, H. G. Sterrett, J. E., 1935 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Burke, T. V., Wiesenberger, Arthur; Angell, James W. Stock, 1941-1961 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Ballantine, Arthur A.; Borthwick, H. R.; Crum, W. L.; Dean, Arthur H.; Dohr, James L.; Fernald, F. E.; Hird, William H.; Nissley, Warren W.; Paton, W. A.; Rathbone, Albert; Sanders, T. H.; Staub. Walter A.; Tietjen, A. C.; Woods, Homer S.; CHECK IF FILED UNDER Stock [Stock Dividends], INMAGIC (Box 69)
      - Carey, John L. Stock Options, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Brundage, Percival F.; Dohr, James L.; Herrick, Anson.; Reed, Philip D.; Robinson, W. S.; Slichter; Sumner H. Study Group on Business Income, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Broad, S. J.; Brundage, Percival F.; Study Group on Business Income (includes Report of the chairman of the committee on the study of business income, its concepts and terminology), 1948 (1) (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Brundage, Percival F.; Denison, Edward F.; Garrett, A. A.; Nourse, E. W.; Court, Andrew T.; Crowther, Geoffrew; Stevens, W. H. S.; Study Group on Business Income, 1948 (2-10) (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Barkin, Solomon; Blough, Ray.; Brundage, Percival F.; Copeland, Morris.; Garrett, A. A.; Bray, F. Sewell; Broad, Samuel J.; King, Earle C.; Angell, James W.; Warburton, Clark; Willits, J. H.; Study Group on Business Income, 1948 (11-22) (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Norris, Harry.; Peloubet, Maurice E.; Sanders, Thomas H.; Davenport, Jonh; de Paula, F. R. M.; Inglis, John B.; Jacobus, Alma.; Jacobus, Alma.; Norton, Paul T.; Wilcox, Edward B.; Study Group on Business Income, 1949 (1-9) (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - Bowers, Edison L.; Brundage, Percival F.; Carey, John L.; Clay, Henry.; Gregory, E. R.; Jacobus, Alma.; White, Erskine N.; Katona, George.; Likert, Rensis; Nourse, Edvin C.; Sanders, T. H.; Smith, Charles W.; Study Group on Business Income, 1949 (10-19) (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Andrews, T. Coleman.; Brundage, Percival F.; Dohr, James L.; Heyworth, Geoffrey.; Jacobus, Alma.; McCool, Hazel M.; Alban, Sir Frederick;Hancock, John; Katona, George.; Knauth, Oswald.; Sutherland, Malcolm; Smith, Charles W. Study Group on Business Income, 1949 (21-23)-1950 (1-7) (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - Brundage, Percival F.; Engelmann, Konrad.; Gilman, Stephan.; Smith, Charles W.; Graham, Willard; Jennings, Alvin R.; Steward, A. J. Study Group on Business Income, 1950 ( 8-13)-1951 (1-4) (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Brundage, Percival F.; Peloubet, Maurice E.; Paton, William A. Macmillan Company. Study Group on Business Income, 1951 (5-14) (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Burke, T. G.; Cannon, Arthur M.; Norman, H. G.; Gilman, Stephen; Littleton, A. C.; Ross, Clarence W.;; Stanley, Hubert W.; West, Phillip; Whitney, William H.; Willits, Joseph H.; Study Group on Business Income, 1951 (15-22) (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Brett, George.; Blackie, W.; Copeland, Morris; King, Earle C.; Sanders, T. H.; Sheere L.; Fabricant, Solomon.; Hill, Thomas M.; Study Group on Business Income, 1951 (23-31) (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Blough, Carman G.; Brundage, Percival; Dean, Arthur H.; Dean, Joel.; Holme, Stanley A.; Ross, Clarence.; Armory, Derek; Moonitz, Maurice.; Sneath, R; Willits, Joseph H.; Study Group on Business Income, 1951 (32-35)-1952 (1-6) (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Bray, F. Sewell; Brett, George; Clay, Henry; Crowther, Jeffrey; Jones, Ralph C.; Willits, Joseph H.; Study Group on Business Income, 1952 (7-16) (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - McNichols, Thomas J.; Bray, F. Sewell; Carey, John L.; Clay, Henry; Inglis, John B.; Jones, Ralph C.; Nye, Paul E.; Paton, William A.; Seidman, J. S.; Spacek, Leonard; Study Group on Business Income, 1953-1960 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Andersen, Arthur.; Farrand, George N.; LeBoeuf, Randall J.; Nissley, Warren W.; Ross, Clarence.; Starkey, Rodney F.; Blackie, W. Surplus, 1930-1950 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Bell, William H.; Blough, Carman G.; Dohr, James L.; Dohr, James L.; Herrick, Anson.; Paton, William A.; Peloubet, Maurice E.; Inglis, John B.; Stans, Maurice; Surplus-Earned Surplus, 1945-1949 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Conover, Louis W.; Alexander, James S.; Broderick, J. Joyce; Frank, Glenn; Gay, Edwin F.; Gilbert, S. P.; Sedgwick, Ellery; Sterrett, J. E.; Warburg, Paul M.; Taxation, 1921-1923 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Adams, T. S.; MacDonald, A. R.; Burling, Edward B.; Winston, Garrard B.; Taxation, 1925-1928 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Adams, Thomas S.; Bishop, Warren.; Mills, Ogden L.; Stark, W. R.; Sterrett, J. E.; Cravath, Paul D.; Covington, J. Harry; Taxation, 1929-1932 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Arthur, Donald.; Dalton, H. G.; Filbert, W. J.; Gerry, Peter G.; Haas, George C.; Hull, Cordell.; Jensen, E. Willard.; Lonergan, A.; Moore, Blaine F.; Morgenthau, Henry.; Roberts, George E.; Roper, Daniel C.; Adams, Mrs. T. S.; Bailey, J. W.; Connaly, Senator T.; Davis, Joseph S.; Dillon, Clarence; King, William H.; Lonegan, Senator A.; May, George O.; McLeod, Aubrey S.; Palmer, Paul; Sutherland, L. G.; Goldman, Sachs US Treasury Department Taxation, 1933-1936 (1-3) (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Angell, Montgomery B.; Bennet, R. B.; Hazlitt, Henry.; Mead, Joseph.; Palmer, Paul.; Adams, T. S.; Elliston, H. B.; Mead, Joseph; Rowland, Stanley W.; Smith, Alfred E.; Tower, Walter S.; Taxation, 1936 ( 4-8)-1938 (Box 70, Folder 14)